Three things I would like to do in the future
Now, let's move on to the three things that Aira would like to do in the future!
What is the first one?
Here is the first one!
Yes!
Race to get a driver's license
I've been saying since about 2 years ago that I would definitely get my driver's license this year.
I've been saying that every year.
But I haven't had a chance to go every year.
I haven't been able to get it at all.
So I really want to get my driver's license this year.
I really want to get my driver's license this year.
Does anyone in Amefura have a driver's license?
No one has a driver's license.
When we go out for fun, we all take the train together.
If I had this, I would love the ocean.
When I have a day off and want to refresh myself, I often take the train to the beach by myself,
I always wish I had a car. So I want to get a car as soon as possible.
It would be nice. Well, the train is nice, too.
I like the train, too.
But by car.
I'd like to play some silly music and sing along the seaside while driving.
How about it? Is it realistically possible?
We are in the process of negotiating.
I'm planning a project to see how many licenses all the members can get.
I'm talking to the manager about how much we could all get if the office would organize it.
There are idols who take pictures individually.
But I don't think I've ever heard of a group filming together.
That's right, we're negotiating with all the members to do a YouTube project that would kill two birds with one stone.
We are negotiating with all the members.
If we film together, maybe we can teach each other what we don't understand.
I'm sure there will be cases where one person won't be accepted.
I think it would be a lot of fun.
If we were to do this with four people...
Who would be good at this?
Driving?
No, it's me.
Me! Me.
If I told this to the other members, they'd probably say I'm not the best.
I'm not good at studying or anything, but when it comes to driving...
I'm probably the safest driver and I know the rules and manners.
I think I'm the best driver because I know the rules and manners.
Why?
Isn't it kind of like that? It has a dangerous vibe.
Dangerous?
I don't mean it's rough.
I don't know... it's more like... a blur.
I think everyone has that image.
By the way, there's a written test.
Were you good at those tests, Ira?
I couldn't do it.
I really couldn't do it.
You know those tests where you have to answer the questions with a marker?
I didn't know what to do.
I'd look at the lance and see, "Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
I'd look at the lance and see four lines, then I'd go on to the next line, then the next line, then the next line, then the next line, then the next line, then the next line, and so on.
I'm just trying to get it right, and if I don't understand something, I sell it at random.
What do you want to do in the future?
Mr. Nissy
Mr. George
Hiroaki
Mr. Mamoru
Thank you very much for watching this program provided by Mr. Fuuji.